<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pasta on recipes</title><link>https://tompreston.github.io/recipes/tags/pasta/</link><description>Recent content in pasta on recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://tompreston.github.io/recipes/tags/pasta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fresh Pasta</title><link>https://tompreston.github.io/recipes/posts/fresh-pasta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tompreston.github.io/recipes/posts/fresh-pasta/</guid><description>5 servings
Ingredients 250 g Semolina Flour 250 g 00 Flour 5 whole Egg Steps Sieve the flour onto a clean surface Make a flour volcano and crack in the eggs Mix the eggs with fork and slowly bring in the flour until you have a dough Roll out the dough and feed it through a pasta machine roller, starting at thickness 0 and work up to 6 Roll through the pasta cutter and, if there&amp;rsquo;s lots, hang it up Boil the spaghetti until al dente (~10 mins) (Add salt to the water first to season the pasta) Notes https://youtu.</description></item><item><title>Spaghetti Carbonara</title><link>https://tompreston.github.io/recipes/posts/spaghetti-carbonara/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tompreston.github.io/recipes/posts/spaghetti-carbonara/</guid><description>5 servings
Ingredients 100 g pancetta (Bacon works too) 50 g / 100 g parmesan 50 g pecorino 3 whole egg 350 g spaghetti 2 whole garlic clove (Peeled and squashed) 50 g butter Steps Boil water Finely chop the pancetta Grate and mix cheeses Beat the eggs and season with grated black pepper Boil spaghetti until al dente (10 mins) (Season by adding 1 tsp salt to water first) Fry butter, pancetta and squashed garlic cloves, until golden (5 mins) Then remove the garlic Turn off the heat Scoop the spaghetti into the pan with a bit of the hot pasta water.</description></item></channel></rss>